Welcome back to my channel, as I have
shown you many videos of the car, so today I am showing you a video
of Tata Punch, in which I had
an accident a few days ago, there was a
slight dent in the left door, so
I will
show that to you, you should subscribe to the channel, as
you can see, it is the left side door, there was
a tree branch on it, due to which there was a dent,
so there was a dent here, there is a
dent here and it has been a long time since it happened with the
latest A1, within a week,
and I have just come to the Tata showroom,
I am claiming it in the workshop, so many
people ask that someone's car bumper bumper was
damaged and from where can I get it repaired, like
mine too, it was damaged before this, I got the
entire car, the front bumper, this
part and this part completely
repaired in the insurance, and I will also
suggest to you people that you should get it repaired
in the insurance because in the rear of the car also I got
this and this Nikki door
repaired in the insurance itself, so this  I am currently
entering the vehicle after checking it here
and they have said it will take 10-12
days.
If they get the part, then
I can get it as quickly as three to four days. But
if it is not available in the showroom or workshop, then
they will have to order the
part. So, I will upload more videos of it
in detail. Today, I have come to
park the vehicle in the workshop.
After that, as soon as I get the vehicle back,
I will make a video again and will
tell you the cost. Mostly, I was
told that only the file charge will be levied. So,
this is the Tata Motor Service
Center in Bhiwani. As I told you, the complete
details of the vehicle.
It will take one to one week or 10 days to get the
vehicle repaired. And you guys
tell me by commenting about your vehicle. Many people
comment to me that if our vehicle is strong, then
what should be done, I will
make a separate video for that. If you want me to
make this favorite video about insurance,
then tell me by commenting and subscribe
to the channel. Tell me by commenting what damage has happened to your vehicle
so that I can make
a video related to it again.  Let's make it
and this is the second time I am making an
insurance claim for the car, so there are a lot of
details which I will share with you
in the next video. I have just made a small
entry video of the
car which I have just brought to the workshop,
so please subscribe to the channel and
tell us the details of your car by commenting,
what damages have you suffered, how many times have you made an
insurance claim.